罗马皇帝才是真庞克
Roman Emperors were the real punks.
都说庞克已死
They said punk is cliche.
听我说那些晚宴
Whatever, let me tell you/about these dinner parties,
尼禄(古罗马暴君)喜欢被下毒
Nero loved to get poisoning.
在晚宴上?
At a dinner party?
- 他就在餐桌上安排了一次/- 我没有演出情绪
- He'd arranged one right at the table ***/- I don't feel like going on that.
真糟
Too bad
俱乐部就是花钱买颓废
'cause that what makes/the club feel  like paying us
书上写的 泰特斯灌醉宾客
This is all in the/book. Titus *** the wine
用琴弦捆住他们的小弟弟
and bind their privates with a cord
嘿
Hey
你买了新吉他?
Hey, you get a new guitar?
46年泪珠版 无瑕疵
46 teardrop issue, not a mark on it.
好
All right
我看看
see it
很不错
that is nice
嘿 嘿
hey hey hey
住手!
Hey,cut it out,man!
- 你这白痴杂种.../- 住手!
- You stupid son of a.../- Come on!
这是块木头!
Hey!It's a hunk of wood,bro!
就应该像块木头
It should look like a hunk of wood.
我们不是交响乐团
We're not the philharmonic.
看 这样好多了
See,look,man,it's better already.
嘿 10:45了
Hey!It's 10:45.
去舞台上发泄
How 'bout taking that onstage?
现在有点情绪了
Now I feel like going on.
你是我的孩子 4胞胎也是
You're my child,and/so are the quadruplets.
我不会放弃任何一个
And I'm not gonna give any of you up.
不准像我妈一样说话
Don't you...Talk to me as a mother.
门上标着: 私事关门
Sign on the door says/"closed for private event."
你一个人
You're alone.
还能多私人?
How much more private can you get?
能给我递张纸巾?
Can you pass me a tissue?
你要留谁 10天前该决定了
Who are you keeping?You owed/me a decision ten days ago.
全忘了
Total amnesia.
你是我生活的全部
You're my whole life.
你
You.
Luisa maria不知道该不该留着4胞胎
Luisa maria can't decide if/she's gonna keep the quadruplets.
她留着了 我在网上看了剧本
She keeps them.I read it online.
现在你高兴啦?
You happy now?
告诉你结局让你没得爽
I ruined it for you.
- 周五前要定下2人/- 好
- I want two names by friday./- Fine.
我周四会安排个病人得神秘疾病
I'll arrange for a patient with a/mysterious illness to come in on thursday.
对 你需要测试
Yes,you need more tests.
才过了2个月
It's only been two months.
谁知道他们对反常季节有什么反应?
Who knows how they'll react/to freak weather patterns?
他们在风洞测试里表现不错
They all did fine in the wind tunnel.
周五前定下2人/否则多出的工资在你那扣
Two names by friday,or the pay/overruns come out of your salary.
我会伤害你的 我现在知道了
I can hurt you.I know that now.
我还会把你的停车位移到"e"区
And I move your parking/space to the "e" lot.
别离开我 妈
Don't ever leave me,mom.
你手上病得最厉害的是谁?
Hey,who's the sickest/patient you've got?
有个10分钟之内死的
I've got a guy who'll be/dead in the next ten minutes.
你指能经得起诊断折腾的
Oh,you mean someone who might/actually survive a diagnosis.
这里没有
There's nothing here.
只是一般的爆头 枪伤和假警报
Just the usual cracked/heads,gunshots,false alarms.
要是你会选哪些留下来?
Who would you pick to fill/your narrow little flats?
我推荐谁 你就炒掉谁?
So you can fire them/off of my recommendation?
不错
Nice try.
在这该找谁提供铺床服务啊?
Hey,who do I have to grope to get/some turn-down service in here?
Jimmy Quidd 庞克摇滚歌手
Jimmy quidd.He is a punk rock singer.
你该说庞克摇滚歌星
Punk rock star to you.
多重 外伤 自残 发烧 关节痛/胸廓扩张 疲劳 贫血
Repeated trauma,self-cutting,fever,arthralgia,hyper-inflated/chest,fatigue,anemia.
便血尿血
Blood in the stool and urine.
我肯定是死了 到了诊断天堂
I've died and gone to diagnostic heaven.
血检显示有酒精 可卡因 安非他命 鸦片
His blood results show/booze,cocaine,amphetamines,opiates.
唯一神秘的地方就是他怎能活到38岁
The only mystery here is/how he made it to be 38.
- 我才28岁/- 还说谎
- I'm 28./- And he lies.
他是个肉中刺
And he's a pain in the ass.
- 嘿.../- 打包起来
- Hey,come.../- Wrap him up.
我外带
I'll take him to go.
眼花缭乱的症状
Dizzying array of symptoms.
都可由吸毒外伤和做人失败引起
Any of which could be caused/by drugs,trauma,being a loser.
他个是走动的药罐子 啥都有可能
The guy's a walking/pharmacy.Could be anything.
忘记说了...
Oh,forgot to mention...
这是最后考试
Final case.
对了 就能被聘用
Get it right,you're hired.
贡献紧随其后的 能得亚军席位
Runner-up will be decided strictly/on some definition of merit.
- 心内膜炎/- 肺和肠出血伤
- Endocarditis./- Hemorrhagic lesions in the lungs and gut.
闭塞性细支气管炎/他湮灭在自己喷出的烟雾中
Bronchiolitis obliterans.He/smoked his airways into oblivion.
- 心内膜炎/- 我刚说过了
- Endocarditis./- I already said that.
你说之前我就想到了
I'd heard of it before you mentioned it.
速度也算 说点别的
Speed counts.Find something else.
- 可能是细菌性脑膜炎/- 你已经选了一项病因
- Could be bacterial meningitis./- You already picked.
- 那我选脑膜炎/- 晚了 去测试吧
- I'll take meningitis./- Too late.Go run your tests.
不 他有病是因为他的毒瘾
No,he's sick 'cause he's a drug addict.
不 他符合所有瘾君子的症状
No,he has every symptom/you'd expect of a drug addict.
所以你觉得太完美了?
So you think it's all too perfect?
有别的病想逃过法眼?
Some other disease is trying/to throw us off its trail?
20个症状中4个 那他是个普通的瘾君子
If he had 4 out of 20 possible/symptoms,he'd be a garden-variety druggie.
20个全中 肯定有潜在疾病
20 out of 20,there's/an underlying disease.
- 去做测试/- 不
- Run your tests./- no.
他很虚弱 正在戒毒 刚吐血了
He's weak,in/withdrawal,just spewed blood.
他们还要扯点肺 塞器械进他喉咙 挖肠子
They're gonna rip off a piece of his lung,ram instruments/down his throat,and roto-rooter his intestines.
如果在找病因时没把他整死/就谢天谢地了
It'd be nice if we didn't kill him/trying to figure out what's killing him.
一次按一种诊断做一项测试
One diagnosis,one test at a time.
血氧饱和度低  胸廓扩张
O2 stats are low.Hyper-inflated chest.
- 需要支气管镜检来.../- 扣你2分
- I need a bronchoscopy to.../- You just lost two points.
为什么?
What for?
因为你争着要第一个来
For thinking it makes a/difference who goes first.
- 只有一个正确答案/- 什么分数?
- Only one person can be right./- What points?
只有数字是最客观
Can't have an objective system/of measurement without numbers.
这都不知道 扣3分
You lose three for not knowing that.
现在始 谁拿着这个才能治病 做测试
From now on,only the person/holding this can treat or run tests.
本来想用斧头蛇杖的 我忘车里了
I wanted to give you the serpent staff with/the poison axe head,but I left it in my car.
不需要你
Don't need you.
玩游戏决定请谁 那是一回事
It's one thing to hire based on a game.
不需要你说教
Don't need your lecture.
用游戏决定治疗 那就是疯了
It's insane to treat based on a game.
你得用长远的眼光看问题
You're not taking the long view.
长远得看到病人装进裹尸袋?
The one where we stuff/another patient in a body bag?
不 治错了 他离死可不远
No,if we're wrong,it'll/come pretty fast.
长远的目标是构建精英团队
The long view is the one/where we pick the best team.
省下的裹尸袋可以充当购物袋
That way we can use all the bags/we save for grocery shopping.
这样说服不了你?
You're not buying that argument,are you?
不
no.
这样的话 还是老话吧
In which case,I'm back/to my original position.
不需要你
Don't need you.
怎么看Amber?
What do you think of amber?
我断错症了
I screwed up a diagnosis.
你不太失落嘛
You don't seem that upset by it.
3个月前诊断一个男人患了腺癌
Diagnosed a guy with/adenocarcinoma three months ago.
告诉他还能活6个月
Told him he had six months.
现在你要告诉他来不及圣诞购物了
So now you've got to tell him that he's/way behind on his christmas shopping.
他没恶化
He didn't get worse.
我重新检查过了
I re-checked everything.
活检是假阳性
Biopsy was a false positive.
吸入滑石粉引起的无害创伤
Harmless lesions cause/by talc inhalation.
从宽发落
Medical clemency.
有趣
Interesting.
为什么非得用这个词?
Why would you use that word?
因为我感兴趣
Because I'm interested.
当我感兴趣/我用有趣来形容让我感兴趣的东西
When I'm interested,I describe the things/that make me interested as interesting.
大多数人会说好 或者真棒
Most people would say/good,possibly great.
- 为什么你不能感到欣慰?/- 难道没有别人单单感到有趣?
- Why aren't you able to just enjoy.../- Why aren't other people able to just be interested?
- 他在里面?/- 是的
- Is he in there?/- Yeah.
为什么你坚持吸毒观点?
Why'd you go right/for the drug theories?
要是他有注射癌细胞的习惯/我就猜是癌症
If he had a history of shoving cancer/into his veins,i'd have guessed cancer.
好吧 你是个白痴
Okay.You're an idiot.
要不你怎会让烟鬼带着氧气瓶单独上厕所
Either that or you've decided you can trust a smoking/addict alone in a bathroom with an oxygen tank.
新的测试结果出来了
I got your new test results back.
抱歉来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
你这位同事是...?
Who's your colleague?
- House医生.../- 怎么 Wilson医生?
- Dr. House.../- Yes,Dr. Wilson?
我真的不需要会诊意见
I really don't need the consult.
我知道病情
I know the prognosis.
明显不知道
Apparently not.
Mckenna先生 我要说的实在惊人
Mr.Mckenna,I can't believe/i'm able to say this,but...
你没患癌症
you're cancer-free.
活检像是腺癌 但并不是
The biopsy looked like/adenocarcinoma,but it wasn't.
只是肺部一点无害创伤
Harmless lesions on your lungs.
你没事了
You're fine.
我不明白
I don't get it.
- 酷/- 不 这...
- Cool./- No,it's... it's...
我知道你很震惊 但我反复检查了
I know this must come as a shock,but/I've double-checked the labs.
我刚同意卖了房子
I just accepted an offer on my house.
还办了3次告别晚会
I've had three good-bye parties.
买了去威尼斯的机票
I'm buying plane tickets to venice.
你活着也一样能用啊
You can still use those if you're alive.
不卖房 我还得照付6000美元房产中介费
I have to pay a $6,000 broker/commission on a house I'm not selling.
我可没钱
Money I don't have.
谢谢...
Thank you...
你告诉我
For letting me know.
我原以为只要活着 多花点钱都值得
I- I would have thought the living would mean more than the expenses.
这与钱无关
It's not about the money.
我有17分?
I have 17 points?
我从100分开始扣的
I started you all out on 100.
你把楼内一角给炸了
And you blew up part of the building.
Foreman在哪?
Where's foreman?
- 他收到传呼/- 谁传的 是不是我们的...
- He got paged./- By who?Is it about our...
我传的
By me.
我需要他
I need him right away.
到别的地方去
Somewhere else.
我们要躲着Foreman?
We're hiding from foreman?
Foreman指控我把治疗当儿戏
Foreman accused me of playing/games with patient care.
眼球接下来给谁?
Who gets the eyeball next?
我还没测试呢 仍然有可能是肺的问题
I haven't run my test yet.It/still might be a lung issue.
你不能测试了
You can't run your test.
病人吸入大量浓烟
The patient had massive/smoke inhalation.
做支气管镜检可能会引发喉痉挛
Do a bronchoscopy,it'll/set off a laryngospasm.
我可以做开肺活检啊
I'll do an open-lung biopsy instead.
因为自己搞砸了就做入侵性手术??
You want an invasive surgery/because you screwed up?
是病人偷带烟的
The patient snuck a cigarette.
病人是个瘾君子
The patient is an addict.
他控制不了毒瘾不是他的错
It's not his fault he's jonesing/for whatever he can get his hands on.
控制不了毒瘾不是他的错?
Not his fault he's jonesing?
什么狗屁不通的话?
In what universe does/that make any sense?
给他贴尼古丁贴片
Get him on a nicotine patch.
这样就能对付一下毒瘾
It'll keep up with his jones.
做活检吧
Do your biopsy.
最终考试有什么进展?
How's the new us's final case going?
是个移动靶子
It's a moving target.
House不断转移阵地 让我找不到
House keeps moving/it so I can't find it.
这么说...
So...
你打算专注于解决/达尔富尔(苏丹战乱区)问题
you've decided to focus on/solving the problem in darfur.
Taub在那做活检准备
Taub is in there prepping/the patient for a biopsy.
接近Taub也就接近House
Stay close to taub,or/stay close to house.
就能监视游戏
And stay close to the game.
我想要阻止这场游戏
I'm trying to stop the game.
这就是你在游戏中的角色
That's your role in the game.
你是为了烦我才晃悠到这里来的?
You wander over here to annoy me?
你没穿白大褂
You're not wearing a lab coat.
- House也不穿白大褂 对吧?/- 见鬼!
- House doesn't wear one,does he?/- Damn!
被呼叫 我现在要走了/可也被你烦得够呛
Now when I walk away,it's gonna look like/I have a reason other than just annoyance.
他不让我们帮他准备活检
He won't let us finish/prepping him for the biopsy.
那只手臂试过了吗?
You try the other arm?
不是手臂问题 是他根本不愿意
The problem's not the/arm,it's the entire patient.
嗨
hi.
他让你检查前胸
He let you check his chest.
以及其他任何部位 除了那只手臂
He let you do anything/except check that arm.
他胳膊上全是尼古丁贴片
He wallpapered himself/with nicotine patches.
叛逆也得有个谱
Real rebellion has a point.
不止是年少轻狂和漫无目的
It's not juvenile and purposeless.
我的人生目标就是漫无目的
Maybe purposelessness is my purpose.
你的目标实现了
Mission accomplished.
Amber...
贴片无关 他体内有血凝块在移动
It's not the patches.He's got/blood clots moving through his body.
这么说...
Means...
我错了
I was wrong.
血凝块如果移动到心肺 会有生命危险
If a clot reaches his lungs/or his heart,it'll kill him.
我没说错
It's true.
是没错 你在浪费时间
We all know it's true.You/just wasted our time.
那你又在干吗?
And what you're doing?
- 参加竞争的又不是我/- Taub去哪了?
- I'm not competing./- Where's taub?
Foreman跟着他呢
Foreman was following him.
所以你又呼了Taub
So you paged taub.
不然我还能怎么办
Didn't see that I had much choice.
血涂片里有裂红细胞
He has schistocytes in his blood smear.
说明是DIC(弥散性血管内凝血)导致了血凝块
Which means the d.i.c.'s/causing clotting.
可又是什么导致了DIC呢?
What's causing the d.i.c.?
- 毒品污染/- 刚才那回合你已输了
- Drug impurities./- You lost your round.
新症状新回合 肯定与毒品有关
New symptom,new round.This/has to be drug related.
医生就是这样害死病人的
This is how doctors kill patients.
- 总是忽略事实 想当然/- 瘾君子吸毒是想当然?
- By seeing the stereotype instead of the truth./- Drug addicts use drugs is a stereotype?
毒品有害是想当然?
Drugs are bad is a stereotype?
- 失败者.../- 疟疾
- Losers lose is.../- Malaria.
他好几年没出过境了
He hasn't left the country in years.
疟疾会复发
Malaria's relapsing/recurring.
他可能已患病好几年了
For all we know he could/have been sick for years.
这不仅符合DIC的症状
It explains not just the d.i.c.
还有出血 疲劳 发烧
And the bleeding,but/the tiredness,fever.
...所有被我们归结到毒品上的症状
Everything we attributed to drugs.
是啊 这个搞庞克的家伙/染上疟疾的可能性比吸毒大?
Oh,yeah,it's much more likely that this ass/punk rocker was exposed to malaria than drugs?
如果你总是对的 那刚刚就不会错了
If you were always right,then/you wouldn't have just been wrong.
不会让他用尼古丁贴片过毒瘾
Or let the patient mainline nicotine.
不会糟蹋了眼球模型/那是我高分通过医学考试 外婆给的奖励
Or ravaged my anatomical model,which/grandma house bought me when I aced my mcats.
那是周二一个医药代表拿来的
A pharmaceutical rep/left that here on tuesday.
我外婆做兼职
Grandma does some part-time work.
那个美女才三十来岁
The rep was a 30-something babe.
谢谢 我屁股像她
Thank you.I got her hips.
自豪地获胜
Carry it with pride.
蛇蝎女 进入败部复活
Manipulative bitch,you're/wanted in the loser's circle.
你为何讨厌瘾君子?
Why do you hate drug addicts?
你的情况不一样
Your situation is different.
你按处方用药
You're taking a necessary prescription.
我知道...我棒极了
I know...i'm fabulous.
我也不是那个病人
And I'm not the patient.
我不能对瘾君子有意见吗?
I'm not allowed to have/a problem with junkies?
可以
You're allowed.
但总有个原因
There's gotta be a reason.
他是个病人 和你素不相识
He's a patient.You don't know him.
而你却厌恶他
But you hate him.
他在虚度人生
He's throwing his life away.
因为他有自己的准则?
'cause he's setting his own terms?
不必整天担心随堂测验?
Not living in fear of every pop quiz?
我们不是在讨论他吗
I thought we were talking about him.
和他一点关系也没有
We were never talking about him.
你为什么害怕失败?
Why are you afraid to lose?
你想解雇我 就因为我太好胜?
Are you gonna fire me/because I like to win?
想知道原因而已
Just want to know the reason.
我看过场足球比赛
I watched this football game once.
发现了一个奇怪的现象
And I noticed something odd.
踢赢了的队伍比较快乐
The winning team was the happy one.
所以选择赢
I did the math.
这个病人也很快乐
Our patient's happy.
他是个白痴
He's an idiot.
他是个快乐的白痴
He's a happy idiot.
他颠覆了你的世界观
That screws with your world view.
失败可以让人如释重负 不是吗?
There's something freeing/about being a loser,isn't there?
- 你为什么害怕.../- 因为妈妈不够爱我
- Why are you afraid.../- Mommy didn't love me enough.
爸爸对我期望太高
Daddy expected too much from me.
之类的!
Something!
即便如此
Let's assume that's true.
我知道我在你们看来有缺陷
I get how that can make/me a screwed-up person.
如果我不择手段是为了追求真相/这对病人又有什么坏处?
But how is my willingness to do anything/to get the right answer bad for my patients?
或者换句你容易理解的话来说
Or put in terms you can understand,
你觉得这么做有错?
how is it bad for you?
我没让你去拿药
I didn't ask you to pick up the meds.
我想做个好同事
I'm trying to be a good colleague.
你帮House开药 换取高分
You're trying to boost your score/by prescribing drugs for house.
要不怎么会有两个袋子?
Why else would you have a second bag?
我又没说是要做你的好同事
Didn't say good colleague to you.
你没忘记手上还有个病人吧
You realize we still have a patient.
才不关心那个病人
Don't care about the patient.
你关心自己的饭碗多过他的死活?
Do you care about this job more/than you care about his life?
我关心自己的墙纸多过他的死活
I care about my wallpaper more/than I care about his life.
得了 别忽悠我了
Okay,you're jerking me around.
- 作为一个医生 你不可能.../- 我珍惜生命
- There's no reason to be a doctor if you don't.../- I care about life.
可我不在乎他的生命/他自己都不在乎 我干吗要?
I just don't care about his.He/doesn't care.Why should i?
- 我宁可花些时间来.../- 拍老板的马屁
- My time is better spent.../- Kissing up to your boss.
一般医生在一个病人身上只花十八秒/他只有这么多时间
Average doctor cuts off a patient 18 seconds into/a history because that's all the time he's got.
可我们六人却围着个一心求死的人瞎忙活
Meanwhile six of us are ministering/to a guy with a death wish.
那你干吗做这份工作?
So why do you want the job?
总之不是想为人民服务
Not because I'm maximizing/my service to mankind.
有你的
Good for you.
他去哪了?
Where is he?
我们得花一小时去找一个存心消失的人
We're gonna spend the next hour looking/for a guy who doesn't want to be found.
Jimmy Quidd "精"选集
jimmy quidd's greatest stiff.
1989年
1989.
哪个不想赚钱的公司发行的?
A profit-seeking entity released this?
他自己出的钱
Put it out himself.
很显然 他希望有人听 却不指望有人欣赏
He wanted people to listen,but apparently/didn't want people toenjoylistening.
- 那 为什么.../- 确实想不通
- Now,why would someone.../- Truly a mystery.
为什么有的人偏是要惹人厌呢?
Why would anyone do something/just to aggravate people?
为什么你桌上有张免责声明的表格
Why would you have a blank/liability release form,
还有支票本?
plus your checkbook,on top of your desk?
它们本来装在信封里/信封在抽屉里 上面还压了本书
Probably because they were in the second/drawer in a manila envelope under a book,
是你把它们摆到了桌面上
and you put them on top of my desk.
你一向把支票本放在家里
You usually keep your checkbook at home.
这样就可以找借口不借钱给我
It's your go-to excuse for/why you can't lend me money.
你打算赔那家伙六千块钱 是吧?
You're gonna pay the guy/the six grand,aren't you?
我不能给别人开支票吗
There are other people/I write checks to.
我得交有线电视费啊
I do have cable.
过失难免带来损害
There's no negligence without injury.
我给这家伙下了死亡通知
I handed the guy a death sentence.
让他痛苦的不是死刑
He's not distressed/with a death sentence.
而是无期徒刑
He's distressed with a life sentence.
我让他痛苦了三个月
I gave him three months of misery.
你给了他全新的三个月
You gave him three months/of being someone special.
要不是你 他还会一如既往的沉闷下去/你还要给他钱?
You're paying the guy because he used to be/boring,and without you he's gonna be boring again.
嗨
hi.
疟疾检测的结果出来了?
Results of the malaria test already?
呃 不是
Well,no.
想问 你有没有送他去做别的...
But we were wondering if you'd sent/the patient for any additional...
检测
Tests.
你们把病人弄丢了
You lost the patient.
Taub 去查失物招领处
Taub,you check lost and found.
13...
Thirteen...
你跟我来
come with me.
你为什么喜欢瘾君子?
Why do you love drug addicts?
我对待病人一视同仁 所以...
I won't pigeonhole the/patients,so that means I'm...
我知道该下什么结论
Perfectly capable of/drawing my own conclusions.
你知道怎么回答问题吗?
Are you capable of answering a question?
我认为他的问题不仅仅是毒品
I think there's more/to him than the drugs.
有见地 何以见得?
Admirable.Why?
有见地需要理由吗?
I need a reason for/doing something admirable?
凡事都有理由
There's always a reason.
他是病人 你不了解他/为什么向着他?
He's a patient,you don't/know him.Why do you like him?
父母酗酒 还是年少时也吸过毒
The alcoholic parent,druggie youth.
不会有 没过去的圣人
There's no such thing as/a saint without a past.
也不会有 没未来的罪人
Or a sinner without a future.
你凭什么确定/吸毒是其他问题的掩饰?
What makes you so sure that drugs/are a mask for something else?
吸毒从来都是其他问题的掩饰
Drugs are always a/mask for something else.
这是我这辈子听到最蠢的话
That's the dumbest thing/I've heard in my life.
你真想要这份工作?
You really want this job?
你认为你能劝我离开?
You think you can talk me into leaving?
你喜欢有隐私空间/老板却要了解一切
You're a person who likes her privacy working/for a man who needs to know everything.
你在意病人安危 老板却在意游戏
You're a person who cares about her patients/working for a man that cares about games.
我听见他的声音了
I hear him.
既没有暴风雪 也没有冰雹/不用惧怕黑夜
So neither sleet nor/hail nor dread of night.
等等...
Wait,wait,wait...
疟疾不会传染
Malaria's not contagious.
孩子们 我祝你们...晚安!
Children,I bid you...Good night!
我走了!
And I'm off!
你们谁吸取了我的力量?
Which one of you guys sapped my powers?
是你吗?
Was it you?
是你夺走了我的力量吗?
Did you take my powers?
也许是你 没关系
Maybe it was you.Well,no matter.
我已经感觉好多了
See,I'm feeling stronger already.
没事
It's okay.
没事 他没事
It's okay.He's okay.
呼吸正常 脉搏有力
Respiration's good,pulse is solid.
这里需要护士
We need a lot of nurses in here.
Cuddy医生
Dr. Cuddy.
教千军尽哀的容貌/(引自荷马史诗)
That face that launched/a thousand long faces.
看好你的病人
Get control of your patient.
实在不行 就把他绑在床上
Strap him to the bed if you have to.
我想4个都留下
I want to keep all four.
只能雇俩
You can have two.
你不懂谈判怎么妥协 对吗?
You don't get negotiation,do you?
我说4个 你说3个/最后达成一致 3个半
I say four,you say three,we/finally settle on three and a half.
这对Taub来说是个好消息
Which would be good news for taub.
你不想要4个 也不想要3个
You don't want four.You/don't want three.
如果我说3个/你就可以继续玩游戏了
But if I say three,you get/to keep playing your game.
你会选谁?
Who would you pick?
你在问我意见?
Are you asking my opinion?
如果你有绝对真理 会更好
If you have any absolute/truths,that would be even better.
你从不愿听我意见
You never want my advice.
你这辈子都在试图回避我的意见
You spend your life/trying to avoid my advice.
你是一场官僚主义噩梦
You're a bureaucratic nightmare,
永远那么难搞 最多是个二流医生
you're a chronic pain in the ass,and/you're a second-rate doctor at best.
我脸红了吗?
Am I blushing?
不过 你的确...
But you do...
对用人的事儿很在行
Know this stuff.
咱们能把这事儿说完吗 选谁?
Can we get this over with?
Taub和Kutner
Taub and kutner.
Taub不会顺着你 你不喜欢他/但会尊重他
Taub will stand up to you.You won't/like him,but you'll respect him.
Kutner和你有相同的医学哲学
Kutner shares your/philosophy of medicine.
天知道 你这样的 我不需要第二个/不过他真的会帮上你
God knows I don't need two of/you,but he will actually help you.
不是疟疾 血液检查呈阴性
It's not malaria.Bloodwork's negative.
但找到弥散性血管内凝血的病因了/坏血碎块
But we did find the reason for/the d.i.c.Bad blood fragments.
如果能弄清楚碎块怎么...
If we can figure out/how they got there...
做爱时血液感染?
Blood exposure during sex?
抗疟药造成的急性溶血?
Hemolysis from the malaria meds?
别猜了
Stop guessing.
会破坏惊喜
You'll spoil the surprise.
如果你想从这家伙套出线索/他可不是袒露心声那一型儿的
If you're looking to get information out of the/guy,he's not exactly the bare-your-soul type.
你们会不会/"来自伊帕尼玛的女孩"这首歌
Hey,I was wondering if you/guys know girl from ipanema.
- 你在做什么?/- 没什么
- What are you doing?/- Nothing.
你们在做什么?
What are you doing?
这是我的 老兄
That's mine,man.
你马上该说不是你的了
Oh,you're gonna be/denying that in a second.
下次得多带些 让大家共享
Next time make sure you bring/enough for the whole class.
他和这家伙共用注射器
He's been sharing needles with this guy.
他注入这家伙的血 血液排异/攻击异体细胞
As he injected this guy's blood,his/own blood attacked it,chewed it up.
结果就是发现的那些碎块
Those were the fragments we found.
那弥散性血管内凝血 不代表什么?
So d.i.c.Was nothing?
得退回到吐血以及那一堆/和毒品或有关或无关的症状上
We're back to bloody vomit and his two/dozen other drug or non-drug symptoms.
重新检查每一项
Re-check everything.
把这俩赶出去 把病人绑在病床上
Throw these guys out,and/strap the patient down.
House!
呼吸衰竭
Respiratory failure.
对你可是好消息 13
Good news for you,thirteen.
毒品肯定不是病因
'cause that is definitely not drugs.
坏血碎块和吸毒有关
The blood clots were drug-related.
咳血和呼吸停止还有待探讨
The coughing up blood and the respiratory/arrests are still on the table.
- 吸粉.../- 如果我认同归咎于吸毒的诊断
- Inhalants.../- If I'd wanted a knee-jerk drug diagnosis,
我会让Foreman参与
I would have told foreman where we are.
他知道我们在这里
He knows where we are.
因为他跟着你!
Because he followed you!
- 我跟着Taub/- 我跟着她
I followed taub.I followed her.
他有出血问题
He had a bleeding problem.
可能引起呼吸停止
That could cause respiratory arrest.
我不原谅他的自残行为/你刚才的话 我当没听见
If I wanted to forgive his drano-drinking/ways,I wouldn't ignore what you just said.
可能是神经系统感染
Could be an infection.
不会 腰椎穿刺没问题
No,the lumbar puncture's clear.
什么腰椎穿刺?
Uh,what lumbar puncture?
你没批准那个检查
You didn't authorize that test.
没错 不过 我现在有检查结果
True,and yet,here I am with the results.
13以为是细菌性脑膜炎
Thirteen thought it was/bacterial meningitis.
我有眼球
And I had the eyeball.
无害检查
It was a harmless test.
病人安危还是值得关注的 不是吗?
The patient's welfare still/counts for something,doesn't it?
扣50分
Minus 50.
慢性肺栓塞能解释呼吸的问题/咳血是来自肺部的
Chronic pulmonary embolism would explain the/breathing problem and the blood coming from his lungs.
- 我会做.../- 不用进行任何测试
- I'll run an.../- You're not running any tests.
他知道不是肺栓塞/病人的D-二聚体水平正常
He knows it's not p.e.s.The/guy's d-dimer's normal.
- 那不排除.../- 被授权做一项检查 她却做了8项
- That doesn't always rule out.../- Go in to run one test,run eight more like she did,find out which one's right.
查出正确的 回来给出聪明的猜测
Then comes back with a brilliant guess.
- 真是这样?/- 不
- Is this true?/- no.
太糟糕了 你本可以因聪明加40分
Too bad,'cause that would have/earned you 40 points for cleverness.
分数给Amber
The points go to amber.
- Foreman 你帮病人做检查/- 没问题
- Foreman,you run the tests./- Sure.
愿为你的游戏帮任何忙
Anything I can do to help your game.
- 他不会做检查 对吗?/- 他不会
- He's not gonna run the tests,is he?/- I don't think so.
我出什么问题了?
So what's wrong with me?
你是问除了你的音乐 还有那些毛病?
You mean besides your music?
当然 我演奏的不是你喜欢的/就不叫音乐了
Oh,well,sure,'cause I don't play your/kind of music,it's not music,right?
我不喜欢你 因为你不是Perry Como/(知名爵士歌手)
I resent you because/you're not perry como.
我不是...为听众演奏 明白吗?
Look,I don't... I don't/play for an audience,okay?
那你站在台上演出/真是个奇怪的选择
Well,then,that stage you/stand on is an odd choice.
我只是...为自己 懂吗?
I just... I do it for me,okay?
不是为你
I don't do it for you.
人这辈子有三种选择
You have three choices in this life.
做个好人 争取 或者放弃
Be good,get good,or give up.
你选了第四种
You've gone for column "d."
为什么?
Why?
简单的答案 是如果不曾努力/就不会失败
Simple answer is if you/don't try,you can't fail.
你真的这么简单?
Are you really that simple?
有些人...喜欢我的音乐
Look,you know,some people...
可绝大多数人受不了
they like my music.most/people can't stand it.
他们只是耸耸肩 无视我
but they just sort of/just shrug and ignore me.
但其中有个别人非得来告诉我
but a few,the feel like/they have to tell me
我搞糟了
what I'm screwing up.
荒废了年岁
you know,what I'm wasting.
他们为什么在意?
why do they care?
你心脏附近有特殊的肿块
you have some peculiar/masses near your heart.
多特殊?
peculiar how?
不像你的音乐/它们会引起情感反应
well,unlike your music,they/elicit some emotional response.
真怪
that's odd.
什么?
what?
你在意我喜不喜欢你的音乐/却不在意自己的生死
you care if I appreciate your music,but/you don't care if you live or die.
也许答案就这么简单
maybe the answeris that simple.
我怎么道歉都不够
I can't apologize enough.
对你 对你的家人
to you,to your family.
也许没什么技术上的责任 但...
there may not be any/technical liability here,but...
你把支票撕了 觉得不该要我的钱?
you're ripping it up because you think/it would be wrong to take money from me?
不该只要这点钱
I think it would be wrong to take/so little money from you.
- 你损失了6000块.../- 你毁了我的生活
- you're out 6,000.../- you ruined my life.
我只毁了你三个月
I ruined three months.
这是我第一次 活在当下
for the first time in my life,I/was living in the present.
因为只剩下三个月时间
'cause that's all there was.
你告我 不是为了错误的诊断/是为了正确的诊断?
you're suing me not for the wrong/diagnosis,but for the right one?
你和律师谈过了吗?
have you spoken to a lawyer?
你给我幸福感觉...
you gave me happiness...
现在又将幸福带走
and then you took it away.
肯定不是栓塞
definitely no emboli.
相当模糊
it's pretty fuzzy.
对于拍照 我觉得我干得不错
hey,for point and shoot/I thought I did okay.
影像模糊 因为他一直在抖/吸毒的后遗症
it's fuzzy because he was still shaking/'cause he was coming down from the heroin.
其他人呢?
where is everybody else?
诊所被隔离了
the clinic's been quarantined.
进来个病人 有类似禽流感症状
a patient came in with/avian flu-like symptoms.
又多50块可花
and 50 extra dollars in spending money.
能再做一次影像检查么?
can you do this echo again?
好了 不知感激 扣5分!
okay,minus five for ingratitude!
没说 "谢谢你 House医生"
no "thank you,Dr. House."
没说 "给你一瓶可待因减轻痛苦"/一句都没有
no "here's a bottle of codeine for/your troubles,Dr. House." oh,no.
我是问 能不能给他点镇静剂/让他不动 然后再检查一遍
I was asking if you could do it again after/giving him a sedative to keep him still.
可以
I could.
这样绝对能看出问题
we'd definitely get the answer.
但镇静剂会减弱他的呼吸驱动
but since the opiates would/decrease his respiratory drive,
他已经呼吸困难了/要我害死病人 扣10分
and he already can barely breathe,minus/ten for asking me to kill the patient.
会不会是先天性缺陷?
what if it's a congenital defect?
心脏上的血管异常?
an anomalous vessel on his heart?
你还记得 心脏负责供血
you know that the heart/does the blood stuff,right?
肺才负责呼吸  是吧?
and the lungs do the breathing.
如果血管缠绕住气管呢?
if the vessel wrapped/around his trachea?
- 你要我做什么?/- 核磁共振血管成像
- what do you want me to do?/- mra.
看能不能得到血管的清晰图像
see if you can get a clear/picture of that vessel.
什么... 等等 为什么?
what... wait... what... what... why?
你说过影像不清晰 因为病人在抖
you said the picture sucked/because the patient was shaking.
核磁共振血管成像会更糟
mra will be worse.
我们必须得到血管影像
we have to get a picture.
你的好点子 还不如不说
you were doing better/before you had a good idea.
没有影像 我们还能怎么看到?
how can we see it if/we don't take a picture?
就像你能看见我吧?
you can see me,right?
我们想看他的心脏
we want to look at his heart.
用眼看
with our eyes.
那是说 我在手术台上害死病人
so I kill the patient/on my operating table.
你继续测试你的队员/我面对Cuddy的暴怒
you get to keep testing your team/and I take the heat from cuddy.
如果病人真死了 没错 那会很棒
if it goes that/way,yeah,that'll be excellent.
他的呼吸情况很糟
his respiratory status/is through the floor.
如果有这样一条血管/咱们没尽快移除
if there's a vessel and/we don't remove it fast,
最好的结果 他也得靠呼吸机活下去
best case,he's on a ventilator for life.
我保证 活不了太久
granted,it'll be a short one.
你觉得我该雇谁?
who do you think I should hire?
你要我当着他的面 告诉你?
you want me to tell you in front of him?
现在要他离开 很不礼貌
it would be rude to/ask him to leave now.
如果你不做手术 病人会死
if you don't do the/surgery,the patient will die.
这与你无关
you'll have had nothing to do with it.
每个人都会认为这与你无关
and everyone will know that/you had nothing to do with it.
每个人都会认为/这是因为你不满House解雇你
and everyone will know that it's because/you were pissed off at house for firing you.
你知道我不是为了那个拒绝
you know that's not why I'm saying no.
但结果会变成那样
but that's how it's gonna play out.
选他和Amber
keep him and amber.
你就会搞定一切
you'll get stuff done.
准备给他做手术
prep him for surgery.
这不是根特异的血管
this isn't an anomalous vessel.
看这些淋巴结
look at these lymph nodes.
太大了
way too big.
这是你看到的肿胀组织
there are the masses you saw.
高压70 低压40 血压急降
70 over 40.He's crashing.
两个单位浓缩红细胞
two units of p.r.b.c.s
- 输多巴胺.../- 他快不行了!
- starting dopamine.../- we're losing him!
你的游戏还好玩吗?
so...how's your game going?
并不是 非赢即输
it's not whether you win or lose.
呼吸衰竭
respiratory failure.
肿大的淋巴结
enlarged lymph nodes.
无论如何 他不会活太久
whatever this is,he's not going/to be breathing much longer.
Foreman在这儿 表示游戏结束了吗?
does foreman being here/mean the game's over?
表示病人快完了
it means the patient's/life is almost over.
随你怎么说
you can call it what you want.
我们快完蛋了 各位!快!
we're done,people!come on!
我要思路 我不在乎是谁说的
I need ideas.and I don't/care who they come from.
你当然在乎 这还是个游戏
of course you do.this is still a game.
还是会 答对了有奖 答错了挨罚
you're still going to reward whoever gets/the right idea,punish whoever's wrong.
雇你想雇的 结束这场游戏吧
hire who you want,get this over with.
13 Kutner
thirteen,kutner.
对不起 回家
i'm sorry.Go home.
- 为什么?/- 没什么
- why?/- it doesn't matter.
- 他刚告诉我 我得.../- 肺功能异常 可能是呼吸窘迫综合症
- he just told me that I've gotta.../- lungs are stiff,could be a.r.d.s.
你们让他体液负荷超载
you fluid-overloaded him.
那样的手术之后 谁的肺都会渗漏/再见
anyone's lungs would leak/after that surgery.good-bye.
- 过敏性休克/- 没支气管痉挛的症状
- anaphylactic shock./- no sign of bronchospasm.
淋巴结会不会是/免疫系统慢性刺激造成的?
what if the lymph nodes are caused by/chronic stimulation of his immune system?
- 毒品杂质会引起.../- 街头毒品总掺着各种东西
- impurities in his drugs could have caused.../- street drugs are laced with all kinds of things.
免疫系统的过度反应能解释一切
an immune overreaction/would explain everything.
毒品引起的
drug diagnosis.
这是你们的诊断
that's what you're going with.
解雇的事儿
that firing thing.
当作一场梦吧
it was all a dream.
去查他从哪里弄到的毒品/毒品里有什么
go find where he gets his/drugs and what's in them.
给他注射二巯丙醇 防止重金属中毒
put him on dimercaprol/for heavy metal poisoning.
竞争起作用了
competition works.
你不打算告诉我谁卖给你毒品的?
so you're not gonna tell/me who sells you drugs?
那有什么关系?
why does it matter?
你要死了 有关系吗?
you're dying.does that matter?
没关系
not really.
我不是成年人
i'm not an adult.
我从不想长大
I never wanted to be.
如果活着是...
so if the choice...
苟延残喘 靠助步架行走
is running out the/clock with a walker...
用便盆
and a bedpan...
你难道不后悔吗?
you don't regret anything?
我确实吸毒无度
well,there was a lot of drugs.
酗酒成瘾
a lot of drinking...
打斗不休
a lot of fights.
其他的我都很后悔
I regret everything else.
你恨我 不是吗?
you hate me,don't you?
对
yeah.
我不在意
I don't care.
你的感受如何?
what's it like?
就是无须感到遗憾
it means you have no regrets.
这声音真教人心神欲裂
kinda sticks in your head,doesn't it?
这家伙真不赖
this guy's amazing.
一个顺耳的音符都没有
there's not one redeeming note.
什么混蛋律师会对委托人说/因为能活下去了 所以得打官司
what sort of a lawyer tells his client/he's got a case because he's going to live?
听说不是所有的律师都像电视上/演得那样有良心
I've heard that not all lawyers are/as ethical as the ones we see on tv.
那不是个有法学学位的家伙
I don't think this guy/even has a law degree.
电视演的大部分人也没有
a lot of the guys on tv don't,either.
我想他有的是医学学位
I think he has a medical degree.
我的经济利益受到威胁
it directly affects my bottom line.
- 你能借我的钱少了.../- 我在承担责任
- you have less money to lend.../- i'm trying to take responsibility!
我就是想教你 每个人都为自己而活
and I'm trying to teach you/that everyone is out for theirs.
你也该为自己打算
you might as well keep yours.
然后把钱借给你?
and lend it to you?
你想控制一切
you have to control everything.
你为什么还要问别人 应该炒了谁
how come you're going around/asking everyone who you should fire?
我在征询意见
i'm asking for input!
我还以为你会对我的谦虚表示赞赏
I thought you would have/admired the humility.
你喜欢游戏 因为你爱掌控游戏
you like games because/you can control them.
天啊 我要把唱片放回去了
oh,god... I'm gonna/put the record back on.
你喜欢有趣的东西/从来不管好坏或者真实与否
you like what's interesting.../never mind if it's real or good.
想知道为什么你给那家伙六千块吗?
wanna know why you/offered that guy six grand?
什么事情都有可能发生/而这让你提心吊胆
life just happens,and that/scares the hell out of you!
你认为你可以治愈痛苦!
you think you can cure pain.
你认为你可以逃避痛苦!
you think you can avoid pain!
你要对一切负责/为病人的无聊生活负责
you think you're responsible for every/failure,every patient's boring life,
- 为朋友的过错负责/- 你和我的病人一样 都不愿面对生活
- ever friend's screwed-up... - you don't/want to face it any more than my patient does.
要死很容易
dying's easy.
活着却很难
living's hard.
用得着这么动人肺腑吗
that can't possibly be/as poignant as it sounded.
还是找不到毒品源 但这不是问题所在
uh,still can't find the drug source,but/I don't think that's the problem.
因为二巯基丙醇不起作用
the dimercaprol isn't working.
还有Quidd在弃儿福利院做义工
and quidd volunteers at/a home for abandoned kids.
你告诉我们这些干什么
why are you telling me this?
他的贝司手告诉我的
because his bass player told me.
- 这和病有关系吗?/- 我不知道
- is it medically relevant?/- I don't know.
- 那你为什么.../- 别玩游戏了 做事吧
- well,then why are you.../- stop playing games and do your job!
不
no.
这次 我要炒掉Taub和Amber
this time,i'm firing taub and amber.
你开玩笑吧 是吗?
this is a joke,right?
如果你们能想出答案/这就只是个玩笑
it's only a joke if you/come up with the answer.
找不出答案 可就不好玩了
it's not really funny if you don't.
13和Kutner 你们也被炒了
thirteen and kutner,you're fired too.
- Foreman/- 他是个瘾君子
- foreman./- he's a druggie.
我不认为有别的疾病
I was never sure there was/a disease in the first place.
我们所知的就是他要死了
so all we know is that he's dying.
谁来告诉病人?
who wants to tell the patient?
好吧 找些孩子去跟他说
fine.we'll get some/kid to go talk to him.
那是和他唯一相处的人
it's the only people he/gets along with anyway.
我们被解雇了吗?
are we still fired?
- 他与被遗弃的孩子在一起?/- 这和病有关系吗?
- he works with abandoned kids?/- is it medically relevant?
我想是的
I think so.
我要做个脑部活检
I need a brain biopsy.
给病人
for the patient.
站住
stop it.
你们俩调个位置
you two switch?
你准备凿开病人的脑袋吗?/他昨天差点死在手术台上
you want to drill into a skull of a patient who/almost died on the operating table yesterday?
他们来这里做甚?
why are they here?
要不是他们 我可找不出这答案
because I wouldn't have gotten/the answer without each of them.
你直接告诉我就得了
you could have just told me.
我想让你有负罪感
I want you to feel guilty.
她认为病人是个失败者
she thinks the patient's a loser.
她认为病人是个赢家/正常的人 正常的毛病
she thinks the patient's a winner; just/a regular guy with a regular problem.
他认为只要他能长大成人 他一切都会好
he thinks he's gonna be/great once he's all growed up.
而他认为...你怎么想来着?
and he thinks...what did you think?
- 自体免疫/- 对的
- autoimmune./- right.
不那么好玩 但是同样重要
less interesting,but just as important.
我们不可能都对
we can't all be right.
你们都错了
you're all wrong.
我妈妈总说错错不会得对
my mom always said that two/wrongs don't make a right.
她没说错了四次叠加会怎样
she never said anything/about four wrongs.
我觉得其中有玄机
I always found that suspicious.
普通旧疾 麻疹
plain old measles.
长期和雾都孤儿们待一块儿
constant exposure from hanging/out with oliver twist and his lot.
他应该接种过疫苗
I assume he's been vaccinated.
病人的免疫系统/在多年的吸毒中已经被摧毁
patient's immune system was/shredded with years of drugs.
早期的症状是皮疹和发烧
they're early markers of rash and fever.
对瘾君子来说不会引起注意
would have been lost in a druggie.
他的免疫系统反应过度/所以身体毛病百出
his immune system overreacted.that's/why his body went haywire.
真不错
that's clever.
没有神经异常 不许做活检
you're not doing a biopsy/without neurological symptoms.
如果我对了 病毒就在他的脑子里
if I'm right,the virus is in his brain.
- 治疗错误 他就没机会了 /- 我需要神经性的...
- wrong course of treatment could be his last course of.../- I need a neurological...
他一直在吞咽
he kept swallowing.
可能是神经性的 好比复杂部分性癫痫
could be neurological.could/be a complex partial seizure.
学给我看看
what did it look like?
很好 天啊 女人
good...god,woman.
你还需要多少证据
how much more proof do you need?
如果你能引起癫痫发作 就能做活检
if you can induce a seizure,you/can have your biopsy.
这是闪光灯
we're gonna use flashing lights.
产生有害的刺激 刺激你的大脑
noxious stimulation,it'll/irritate your brain.
如果确实有神经元的损伤/这会引起癫痫发作 我们就能...
if there's damage to your neurons,it'll/trigger a seizure that we can...
我给带来点更毒的
I got something much more noxious.
这个不常用
it's not as commonly used,
但声音同样能造成刺激
but sound can be just/as big an irritant.
这下感受到你的影响力了
now remind me of your influences here.
使劲听 能发现Thelonious Monk的爵士乐/和垃圾道捣碎机的混合音效
'cause I'm gonna say,thelonious monk and the sound a trash compactor makes when you crawl inside it.
我不是为你做的 是为我自己
I don't do it for you.I do it for me.
你觉得怎样?
what do you think?
他是在癫痫发作呢 还是在跳舞?
is he seizing or dancing?
癫痫发作
seizing.
给他放B面 那更猛 预定手术做脑部活检
play him the b-side.it's even/worse.schedule an o.r.for the biopsy.
讲厅见
see you in the lecture hall.
来点温柔的音乐 增加悬疑感
a little mood music.build the suspense.
更像民谣
sounds more folky.
你真是不知道什么时候该闭嘴
you seriouslu have no idea/when to stup up,do you?
Amber 请起立
amber,please stand.
你没叫我蛇蝎女 是坏事吗?
you didn't call me bitch.is that bad?
玩这个游戏 你比其他人都在行
you play the game better/than anybody else here.
但是动机错了
but for the wrong reasons.
动机不要紧 结果才是唯一...
reasons don't matter.results/are the only thing...
你错了
you were wrong.
20年前 这由Jim Moskowitz录制
20 years ago,this was/recorded by jim moskowitz.
也就是后来的Jimmy Quidd
who later became known as jimmy quidd.
爱孩子 有副好心肠 甚至有灵魂
loves kids,apparently has/a heart,perhaps even a soul.
如果你要为我工作/就得不计错误 不怕失败
if you're gonna work for me,you have to/be willing to be wrong,willing to lose.
你也真的失败了 你被炒了
'cause you just did.you're fired.
13 起立
thirteen,please stand.
你被炒了
you're fired.
- 你才说我的分析是对的.../- 他是个瘾君子
- you just said I was right about.../- he was a drug addict.
四个候选人 两个位子
four applicants,two spots.
如果我能要三个 你就留下来了
if I had three,i'd keep you.
游戏结束
game over.
以后的日子你必须要长大了/你得了麻疹
you're gonna have to grow old/after all.you've got measles.
我们用皮质类固醇给你治疗
we're blasting you with corticosteroids.
- 你怎么了?/- 我被炒了
- what's wrong with you?/- I got fired.
你在这里干啥
what are you doing here?
试着不去在意
trying not to care.
这很难
well,that's not easy.
你又搞什么花样?
what the hell did you do?
你要我雇Kutner和Taub
you told me to hire kutner and taub.
因为我知道你不会的
because I knew you wouldn't.
我不能让你雇两个男人
I can't let you hire two men.
- 现在是你性别歧视了/- 你已经有了Foreman
- now,that is sexist./- you've already got foreman.
他是男的?
is he a dude?
也雇个女人
hire a woman too.
雇两个
hire two women.
你该雇在乎病人的那个
you can have the one that/gives a crap about people.
他俩都在乎
they both do.
好极了
great.
雇13吧
hire thirteen.
你是设下的圈套
this was your plan all along.
好吧 至少游戏结束了
well,at least the games are over.
言之过早了
how long have you known me?